<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Revo::Andrie</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Revo::Andrie</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Andrie</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Andrie de Vries is a data scientist, author and R programmer.
Andrie is co-author of the book R for dummies, the book that helps everyone getting started with R, regardless of prior programming knowledge. He is also a regular contributor to the question and answer site StackOverflow.
He is also a regular speaker at R and industry events, including:
 UseR!2016: Tutorial - Using R with Jupyter notebooks for reproducible research Machine Learning and Data Science conference, Bangalore 2016: Microsoft R Server &amp;amp; Applications: Comprehensive Overview EARL London, 2015: Reproducible Data Analysis with Revolution R Open (agenda) UseR!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using R in a blog</title>
      <link>/blog/2016-12-21-using-r-in-a-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2016-12-21-using-r-in-a-blog/</guid>
      <description>You can do many things with R, including writing blogs and blog posts.
To build this site, I am using the Hugo static website generator, and the blogdown package.
Using R and embedding code in the textThis means I can embed R code directly in the text.
The blogdown::serve_site() function then renders the content automatically (by first running rmarkdown and then letting Hugo build the site).
So I can do this:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hallo World</title>
      <link>/blog/2016-12-20-hallo-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2016-12-20-hallo-world/</guid>
      <description>I have many ideas and explore some of them. But my memory is short, so I tend to forget what I&amp;rsquo;ve done or how to do it.
My intention with this blog is to write down random ideas on a variety of things I work on.
So in this blog I will explore the world of R, machine learning and advanced analytics on Azure Cortana Intelligence Suite (CIS). But expect to get random ideas on Python, software development and other topics.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>